<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrei Stoica - Code Corner</title>
    <link>https://skaterdude97.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrei Stoica - Code Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright 2019 Andrei Stoica</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://skaterdude97.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCI2000</title>
      <link>https://skaterdude97.github.io/pages/csci2000/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skaterdude97.github.io/pages/csci2000/</guid>
      <description> List of reasources for CSCI2000 Tutorial notes:  Tutorial 1 Tutorial 2 - coming next week  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://skaterdude97.github.io/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 15:32:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skaterdude97.github.io/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Code Corner! Welcome to my website/blog. Going forward this will serve as a outlet for me to document and share my experiences as I explore the intricate world of computer science. I will be updating the blog portion of this site as I discover new interesting technologies.
I am currently pursuing a Masters in Computer Science, supervised by Dr Ken Pu. My work focuses on text mining and natural language processing queries in relational databases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://skaterdude97.github.io/pages/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 10:30:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skaterdude97.github.io/pages/resume/</guid>
      <description>Printable single page version here
Education  Bachelor of Science - Computer Science, 2018 Ontario Tech University, Oshawa, ON
 Master of Science - Computer Science, Expected Completion 2020 Ontario Tech University, Oshawa, ON
  Work Experience  Teaching Assistant University of Ontario Institute of Technology (UOIT), Oshawa, ON Sept. 2017 - May 2020 
 Lead classes of 20-25 junior and senior level undergraduate students on in-class activities Corrected student work and provided feedback for improvement Courses: Mobile Devices - Programing Workshop - System Development and Integration - Web Development - Interactive Media - Compilers    Graduate Research Assistant University of Ontario Institute of Technology (UOIT), Oshawa, ON Aug.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://skaterdude97.github.io/csci2000/tutorial01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skaterdude97.github.io/csci2000/tutorial01/</guid>
      <description>Tutorial 01 Getting start with Jupyter Cloud and Linux Jupyter Cloud When you first log in you will be asked to log in with your Google account. Please log in with your @ontariotechu.net account.
Then click the course code (csci2000) to go to your dashboard.
Finaly click on &amp;lsquo;Start My Server&amp;rsquo; and confirm by clicking &amp;lsquo;Launch Server&amp;rsquo;
-&amp;gt; This may take a few moments. Especially if a lot of students are trying to access Jupyter Cloud at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fovorites</title>
      <link>https://skaterdude97.github.io/favs/favs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://skaterdude97.github.io/favs/favs/</guid>
      <description>Relax Youtube | Level1Techs | Hak5 | Tested |
reddit | r/technology | r/science | r/canada | r/worldnews | r/ProgrammerHumor |
Getting Stuff Done School | MyCampus | Blackboard |</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>